herbsmd.com 2010-06-26

# HerbsMD.com -The Privacy Policy Statement

Privacy Policy **Overview**  
Simply, We do not sell, rent or share personal information with any third party. The information you give us is totally confidential, and will not be sold or given to any individual or company or organization under any circumstances. 

The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain and sub-domains of herbsmd.com. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

The HerbsMD Privacy Policy discloses our privacy practices and contains detailed information about the following:

  1. What information of yours does the HerbsMD collect?
  2. What organization is collecting the information?
  3. What are "cookies" and how does HerbsMD use them?
  4. How can you access or edit your information?
  5. What types of security procedures are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your information?
  6. Notice  

**1\. What information of yours does the HerbsMD collect?**  
Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience easier. While you are not required to register for any services on the HerbsMD, Some Products and Services may not function properly or may not be accessible unless you do. 

Information collected online is usually defined as being either anonymous or personally identifiable. HerbsMD collects some information each time a visitor comes to the site so we can improve the overall quality of the visitor's online experience. HerbsMD collects the visitor's IP address (e.g., whether the user is logged on from ibm.com or aol.com), referral data (e.g., the Internet address of the last Web page visited by a user before clicking over to HerbsMD site), and browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform). HerbsMD collects this user information for purposes of product monitoring, product improvement, and targeted advertising. You do not have to register with the HerbsMD before we can collect this anonymous information.

Personally identifiable information refers to data that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name and postal address, which may be collected in addition to the anonymous data described above. HerbsMD collects personal information when you register to use on the HerbsMD, you provide HerbsMD with your name, postal address, ZIP Code, email address, birth date, gender, telephone number, occupation, marital status and other information. While not all of this data is required for our services to function, we are better able to customize your experience if you volunteer complete and accurate information. Users who complete the registration process are given a user account and can take full advantage of the many offerings & Discounts. 

**2\. What organization is collecting the information?**  
When you register for a service within the HerbsMD , that information is generally collected and maintained solely by the HerbsMD unless specifically stated otherwise at the point of collection. 

**3\. What are "cookies" and how does HerbsMD use them?**   
In addition to the personally identifiable information that HerbsMD actively collects when you register, we also collect anonymous information passively using cookies. This technology plays an important role in making the Internet work, but there is much confusion among Internet users about what cookies are and how they are used. 

A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a Web site to the hard drive of your computer so that the site administrator may identify your computer and passively track its activities on the Web site. This unique number identifies your web browser to our computer system whenever you visit our web site . A cookie will not allow a web site to learn any personally identifiable information (such as your real name and address) that you have not otherwise disclosed. 

Cookies allow HerbsMD to automatically remember your web browser when you visit web site. By storing certain registration and preference information on cookies or associating cookies with registration, preference or profile information stored on our computers, we can deliver products and services that use such information more quickly and efficiently for more users. This information is normally saved in an encrypted form that only HerbsMD can interpret.

The use of cookies is an industry standard, and they are currently used on most major web sites. It is possible to adjust your web browser preferences to alert you when a cookie is sent to your hard drive, or to refuse cookies altogether. While HerbsMD does not require you to use cookies, keep in mind that certain features of the web site will not function properly if you set your browser to refuse all cookies. 

**4\. How can you access or edit your information?**  
HerbsMD provides registered users a complete personalized panel. This personalized panel allows users to manage or change their personal information like password, shipping and billing address. User panel also allows users to track their shipment and view order history.

**5\. What types of security procedures are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your information?**  
HerbsMD uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, including "firewalls" and Secure Socket Layers.

**6\. Notice**  
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amend terms on our site. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on our site. In addition, we will notify you in accordance with your Notification Preferences.
